Tufts Daily UP029
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Daily, 1999; UP029.020; 2.4 Linear Feet; 119 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 20; UP029.020.031.00060 (Volume 31)
    [Bill] Bradley, [John] McCain come to Boston. [Timothy] Brooks names director of alumni relations. Fashin and Beauty come to The Daily. [Women's] Tennis expect to win big in '99.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 21; UP029.020.031.00061 (Volume 31)
    Fallout from TCUJ [Tufts Community Union Judiciary] decision threatens chaos in Senate. Hopes resurrected for Fall Fest. Coffee controversy: New Starbucks to open in Davis. Trios offers great dining option. TUTV [Tufts University Television] returns for fall semester. [Women's] Fielf hockey wins first game against Connecticut. [Women's] Volleyball falls for first loss of season.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 22; UP029.020.031.00062 (Volume 31)
    Bill Bradley addresses college students at MIT. Oxfam Cafe, music with activism. [Women's] soccer team nets third shutout. Sailing team surges to successful start. [Men's cross-country] remains confident after loss.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 23; UP029.020.031.00063 (Volume 31)
    Tufts parents respond to '20/20 report. French house blazes environmental path. New biomedical building is delayed. Jumbo's softball coach boosts program in Croatia. Women's cross country cleans up at Fitchburg State. [Men's Soccer] Jumbos out-duel Colby-Sawyer in rain. Football set to kick off 1999 season this Saturday. More than just violence: Rugby team looks to win championship and gain acceptance.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 24; UP029.020.031.00064 (Volume 31)
    Carmichael switches to paper. Tufts protests US Senate budget cut. Supreme Court makes ruling on Student Activities Fee case. Bubs take New York. Political opportunities for students.Golf hopes for good showing in league. This issue also in box 39090011503931y.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 24; UP029.020.040.00025 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
    This issue also in box 39090011477219y.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 27; UP029.020.040.00044 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 28; UP029.020.040.00026 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 29; UP029.020.040.00027 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 September 30; UP029.020.040.00028 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 01; UP029.020.040.00029 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 04; UP029.020.031.00065 (Volume 31)
    Tufts struggles with lull in employment. Incense causes fire in Hillsides Thurs. Stephen Hawking to lecture on campus. Tufts students say they favor reduction in requirements. EPC [Educational Planning Committee] proposes alterations to core requirements. [Jon] Troy, consumate team player, is now record-setting receiver.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 05; UP029.020.031.00066 (Volume 31)
    Hank Azaria returns to Medford. [Michael] Dukakis to speak in Cabot on Wednesday. Study abroad programs offer alternatives. Exhibit tells story of Polish Jewry. Jumbos remain undefeated, face Bowdoin this Sat. [Women's] Tennis feeling singled out.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 06; UP029.020.031.00067 (Volume 31)
    Hindu/Urdu class a success. Trustee Reps selected. Internet advertising to hit Tufts Campus. Russian club comes full circle.Meringue, mariachi, and merriment time. Lack of string players slightly impedes Symphony Orchestra. Jumbos [Women's Soccer] on prowl against the Amcats. [Men's] Cross-Country crusies to victory. Sailing success hasn't been easy.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 07; UP029.020.031.00068 (Volume 31)
    [Michael] Dukakis' casual wit draws in audience. Future of Zeta Psi house being negotiated. TCUJ [Tufts Community Union Judiciary] offered limited representation on ALBO [Allocations Board]. New program gives high school students a CHANCE. Eat well, speak well a la maison francaise. Jumbo Field Hockey loses to Bates Gordon. Jumbo's [Men's Soccer] remain undefeated with 2-0 win over Newbury. Women's cross country continues to run. Tufts crew season begins.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 08; UP029.020.031.00069 (Volume 31)
    New Marxist club active with national parent organization. New organizations leads joint student/community protest. Tufts Republicans debate ending affirmative action. Students express concerns about off-campus housing. Volleyball splits four matches at Bates Invitational.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 12; UP029.020.031.00070 (Volume 31)
    Questions arise after thefts of backpacks. Coalition hopes to heighten awareness. Rallies, lectures to be held for Coming Out Day. Women [Soccer] freeze Polar Bears. Jumbos' [Football] first half offensive success ices Polar Bears.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 13; UP029.020.031.00071 (Volume 31)
    Tufts introduces ID cards. Dr. [Stephen] Hawking dazzles. Students rally for gay pride. Modern-day midwives refute medieval stereotypes, mindsets. Animal rights organization and websites click to promote further awareness. Jumbos [Men's Cross-Country] strong against tough competition, but fall to rivals.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 14; UP029.020.031.00072 (Volume 31)
    Engineering graduate program will soon merge with College of Engineering. Computer shortage in Eaton may be solved in near future. Piano practice makes perfect: Engineers tune up their skills. New Tufts study finds ethnic sterotypes in cartoons. Tufts [Field Hockey] survives grueling stretch. Women's cross country dominated at Wellesley. Jumbos [Men's Soccer] win thriller against Vikings in double over-time. Sailors come on strong: team gaining experience.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 15; UP029.020.031.00073 (Volume 31)
    Hotung Cafe to transform into sports pub following face lift. Tufts radio WMFO switches to digital MP3 audio format. Campus organizations call off political battle spurred by spread of misinformation. Students, faculty fight pollution with Mystic Watershed program. Tufts' 'Mystery Man' provides glimpse of stardom. Enthusiastic new director of choral activities appointed. [Women's] Tennis crushes Brandeis to regain confidence, get on track. Volleyball's losing strak reaches four following defeat at Bowdoin Invitational. Water Polo quietly dominates the region.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 18; UP029.020.031.00074 (Volume 31)
    Former professor of biology Norton Nickerson mourned. Bourgeois opposes School of Americans. Political Science professor Berry wins best book award. Ex-college offers unique alternatives. Tufts' [football] hopes jarred lose on final drive. Lack of running game, four interceptions spel doom for Jumbos [football] against Trinity.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 19; UP029.020.031.00075 (Volume 31)
    Class registration to go on-line. Senate to produce publication. Dirty jobs boycott to kick off in Boston. New Tufts study shows blueberries enhance memory. Reverend's [Scotty McLennan] new book treads spritual path. Jumbo's [Women's Soccer] knock off Bantams in 3-1 come-from-behind victory. Tufts [Women's] tennis wins in dramatic fashion. Tufts [Men's Soccer] loses thriller to Trinity.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 20; UP029.020.031.00076 (Volume 31)
    Students rally against violence. English prof [Andre Dubus III] nominated for book award. Jumbos [Women's Cross-Country] come in 20th place at New-England Championships. Intensity carries Jumbos [Field Hockey] [ast Trinity in shoot-out. [Sailing] team gains experience, momentum builds.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 21; UP029.020.031.00077 (Volume 31)
    UMass professor [Andrew Leong] speaks in favor of affirmative action. Policymaker Abraham Lowenthal speaks about political future of Latin America. Curriculum changes to improve student writing in disciplines. Tufts History professor [Martin Sherwin] makes PBS documentary. [Men's] Cross Country disappoints at the All New England Championships, Tufts fifth among Division III rivals. Jumbos [Volleyball] drop under .500 with loss to Brandeis on Tuesday.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 22; UP029.020.031.00078 (Volume 31)
    Tufts celebrates Halloween '00 with local children. Students gain voice on policy council. Tufts student [Sarah Puglia] pledges to run for Somerville governmental seat. Speed, athleticism spark Frisbee team.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 25; UP029.020.031.00079 (Volume 31)
    Canadian Foreign Minister [Lloyd Axworthy] speaks to Fletcher students. Tufts chapter of Amnesty sponsors concert. 60 concert to travel to Israel for free trip over Winter Break. Pottery, paint, and relaxation. Jumbos [football] come up short.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 26; UP029.020.031.00080 (Volume 31)
    Astronomy examines solar activity. New Masters created. Cheerleaders secure funding. Tufts Mountain Club moves into the open air. Jumbos [Women's Soccer] extend win streak to six before Ephman defeat. Jumbos [Men's Soccer] lose second straight at Williams.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 27; UP029.020.031.00081 (Volume 31)
    Gerald Gill wins CASE Professor of the Year award. Saturday's Kathak performance begins year of dance education. Students to donate meals to charity. Tzedek Hillel encourages community involvement. Career Services to offer Winterships. Jumbos [Field Hockey] extend win streak to four games. Men's cross country upsets MIT at Tufts Invitational. Head of the Charles showing foreshadows a strong spring. [Women's] Tennis closes its season strong.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 28; UP029.020.031.00082 (Volume 31)
    TUPD [Tufts University Police Department] says survey is actually legitimate. Africa and New World minor sponsors film festival tonight. Health Service survey online. Fencing coach slashes and sculpts her way to fame. Struggles continue for Volleyball team. Freshman sailors carrying team to greater success.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 October 29; UP029.020.031.00083 (Volume 31)
    Minority high school students visit Tufts for SCOPE program. Tufts Democrats, GOP active at N.H. presidential town meeting. Religion at Tufts: a gradual evolution. Alpha Phi Delta sells pumkins for charity. Acclaimed author [Dorothy Allison] shares motivation for writing. Tufts, Amherst take intense rivalry into Homecoming. Women's X-Country push to make goals. Jumbo's [Men's Cross Country] attempt overtake Williams. Club sports seeking funding.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 01; UP029.020.031.00084 (Volume 31)
    A Halloween to come home to. Sports award to join homecoming event. A heartbreaking Homecoming: Jumbos drop third straight, fall to Amherst 10-7. Jumbos [football] faked out by Jeff's punt. Quarterback shuffle can't solve offensive woes for Jumbos [football].
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 02; UP029.020.031.00085 (Volume 31)
    PAA [Pan-African Alliance] holds Black Solidarity Day. Film series on the blink for lack of money. Facilities to update systems. ISC [International Scholarship Committee] raises scholarship money for foreign scholarships. Tufts [Men's Cross Country] finishes second at NESCAC championships.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 03; UP029.020.031.00086 (Volume 31)
    VACCESS Health at the fore of national campus vaccinations. Jumbo field hockey slips into ECAC's [Eastern College Athletic Conference]. Tickets soon to be available for [Hank] Azaria. Tufts students contribute to AIDS memorial quilt. Community Health focuses on campus levels of alcohol consumption. TUTV [Tufts University Television] launches into third official season. Tufts [Women's Soccer] drops Homecoming, 2-1. Tufts [Men's Soccer] falls in battle against Lord Jeffs. Field hockey heads to ECACs.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 04; UP029.020.031.00087 (Volume 31)
    New grant to aid in violence prevention. ALAS [Association of Latin-American Students. Harvard professor Christopher Edley says ending racial discrimination not inevitable. Women's cross country finishes sixth at NESCAC championships. Voleyball loses another match. Now it's crunch time [Sailing].
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 05; UP029.020.031.00088 (Volume 31)
    APA [Asian Pacific Americans] holds vigil to protest hate crimes against Asian Americans. New Gantcher Center to open on Monday. Tufts/NEC program's future is secure. Medical professional lectures on Cuban health care system. Call Lasagna the 'father of clinical pharmacology'. Young [Women's Tennis] team takes step forward.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 08; UP029.020.031.00089 (Volume 31)
    University receives $20 million donation to benefit Engineering. New associate Dean of Students named. Greece foreign minister speaks about current Balkan politics. Tufts [football] holds off Colby for victory.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 09; UP029.020.040.00030 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 10; UP029.020.031.00090 (Volume 31)
    Campus leaders train and network over weekend. APSCA [African Political, Social, and Cultural Association] attempting to establish itself. Acquisition of new van will benefit audio-visual group. Women's cross-country team shines at ECAC meet. Big win [Men's cross-country] at ECAC championship boosts the spirit of the men's team.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 12; UP029.020.031.00091 (Volume 31)
    Cartoonist [Garry] Trudeau animates audience. Former Reagan advisor attacks collegiate affirmative action. Students vaccinated against meningitis. Tufts' very own up-and-coming comedian [Xan Franklin] smiles in off-stage life. Jumbo's [Men's Soccer] victory over Bobcats leads to ECAC semifinal berth. Sailors preparing for sun at National Title.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 15; UP029.020.031.00092 (Volume 31)
    Gantcher Center on display. Men's, Women's [Cross country] teams qualify for National Championships. Careening cab crashes into column. Tufts doctor [Carmen Puliafito] helping umpires to keep their eyes on the ball. Universal health care topic of teach-in at the Medical School. Middlebury exacts revenge on Jumbo's [Men's Soccer] in ECACs. Playoff loss to Clark ends strong season [Women's Soccer]. Tufts [football]n looses to Middlebury 22-10, seniors leave disappointed.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 16; UP029.020.031.00093 (Volume 31)
    ALBO [Alocations Board], [TCUJ] Tufts Community Union Judiciary to institute a system of budgetary checks and balances. Tufts students to protest against SOA. Professor [Daniel Dennett] probes into human consciousness. Tufts students take the plunge. Tufts Orchestra set to strike a chord with audiences in Portugal over winter break. Blood drive to aid Someday Cafe owner. Field hockey comes close again.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 17; UP029.020.031.00094 (Volume 31)
    Hollywood hits the Hill. Professors debate the role of democracy and citizenship. [President John] Dibiaggio teaches courses in leadership. Tufts School of Occupational Therapy offers graduate program that helps individuals to help themselves. Sarbande lights up the Supershow. Men's Cross-Country takes secind at NE Regionals. Women [cross-country finish third at NE Championships.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 18; UP029.020.031.00095 (Volume 31)
    Student disciplined for unwanted sexual advance. University considers changing block scheduling. ELBO [Elections Board] looks to better reputation. Students help local victims of doestic violence. Hockey looks to build on last year's success. [Tufts baseball coach John] Casey receives prestigious baseball award. Women's basletball to being new season next weel eith new look. Results mixed for sailing at Atlantic Coasts.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 19; UP029.020.031.00096 (Volume 31)
    Students cheat the registration system. EPS [Education Policy Committee] requirement propsals ready soon. Hip Hop concert will feature Run DMC and Rahzell. Rising [Eden] White lights up the Hill with lecture, award. Tufts hosts storytime for children. Jumbos [Men's basketball] hope to rebound from disappointing system.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 22; UP029.020.031.00097 (Volume 31)
    CIA director [John] Deutsch speaks on US power, security. [Cross-country] Men finish ninth, women 11th at Nationals. New group of Big borthers established.Football finishes inconsistent campaign with an even record. Women [Cross-country] finish 11th at Nationals. Strong [cross-country] men's runners create a dynasty.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 23; UP029.020.031.00098 (Volume 31)
    [Bill] Bradley to unveil foreign policy at Tufts. Tufts-Jumpstart relationship fortified. Shuttle takes students to Logan. Prof. Jane Bernstein: truly a Renaissance woman. Resuorce center provides venue for learning about Tibetan culture. Hockey team defeats Suffol 8-4 in season opener. Men's and Women's squash teams hope to build on last season's strong finishes. Jumbos [men's soccer] finish uneven season. Sailors conclude a successful season.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 24; UP029.020.031.00099 (Volume 31)
    Accessible [President John] Dibiaggio keeps his focus on students. Napster, file sharing software program, is blocked by TCCS [Tufts Computing and Communication Services]. [Women's] Swimming and Diving has high hopes in '99.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 29; UP029.020.031.00108 (Volume 31)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 November 30; UP029.020.031.00100 (Volume 31)
    Students put [Bill] Bradley's foreign policy to the test. Students protest Ga. military school. Campus organizations honor all those lost to AIDS. Men [Cross-country] finish ninth in the nation. Women's X-country gets 11th at nationals.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 01; UP029.020.031.00101 (Volume 31)
    'Geisha' author [Arthur] Golden to speak. Professor [Joel Migdal] discusses prospect of peace between Arabs and Israel. Essence brings its own unique singing style to a capella music. [Men's] Swimming team rides its traditional winning ways.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 02; UP029.020.031.00102 (Volume 31)
    Professors and students react to [Bill] Bradley's visit. Student cars vandalized over Thanksgiving. Festival of lights sparks celebration. Women to begin track season Saturday. Young [men's] track team gets set to defend its new home. Tufts men's squash goes to school on Bard.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 03; UP029.020.DO.00001 (Volume 31)
    J [judiciary] appeals Senate's defiance, TCU [Tufts Community Union] power struggle ensues. PAA [Pan African Alliance] brings speaker to debate Kwanzaa's meaning, direction. Internationally-acclaimed author [Arthur Golden] shares his struggle in writing his magnum opus. Comedian [Joe] Rogen to come to Tufts. Tufts [Men's] basketball improves to 2-2 with a pair of clutch victories.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 06; UP029.020.058.00062 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 07; UP029.020.031.00104 (Volume 31)
    Quad Run, pancake breakfast scheduled for Monday. [Dr. Lisbeth] Grolund gives lecture on national defense. Unconventional post-grad alternatives for seniors. [Rob] LaQuaglia sparks 6-2 rout of local rival Stonehill Saturday. Women's squash exceeding expectations.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 08; UP029.020.031.00105 (Volume 31)
    Senate questions role of Judiciary in government. Shir Appeal recognized on '99 Best of College a cappella CD. Fletcher students attend conference about world peace. Memorial service to be held for [Charlotte Blensdorf] MacJannet: a great benefactor for Tufts and Taillores. Men's track team jumps quickly out of the blocks. Men's swimming splashes its way to a 4-0 record. Karate gets its kicks in fall tournament.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 09; UP029.020.031.00106 (Volume 31)
    Student complaints heard at administrative forum. Website offers students textbook exchange. Speaker highlights tenants, misconceptions of Islamic Religion in Tuesday lecture. Book Celebration honors Tufts faculty publications. Students take on underwater intelligence. Women [basketball] extend win streak to four with 66-48 defeat of Regis. Women tracksters off to strong start. [Women's] Swimming team loses in thrilling finish.
  - Tufts Daily, 1999 December 10; UP029.020.031.00107 (Volume 31)
    Professor [Michael McDowell] ill, class is affected. Tufts ready for Y2K. Open Senate seats are filled. Off-broadway play comes to the Balch Arena this evening. TCU [Tufts Community Union] government heads agree to informal mediation.
- Tufts Daily, 2000; UP029.021; 4.8 Linear Feet; 59 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 January 19; UP029.021.032.00001 (Volume 32)
    Record number accepted early in Round 1. Dowling Hall to be completed in April. Floods strike Hillside 10s and 20s again. Alumnus [Seth Wadley] dies in hit-and-run accident in Washington D.C.. Men's and women's basketball continue with strong play.
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 January 21; UP029.021.040.00032 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 January 25; UP029.021.032.00002 (Volume 32)
    Famed screenwriting professor [Michael Mcdowell] dies over winter break. Professor's [Mark Devoto] avante-garde compostitions premiered at gala affair in his honor. Alumnus [Stephen Distler] endows Ex College with annual buisness course. [Men's] Swimmers meets, now 5-1. Jumbos [Women's swimming and diving] double dip with weekend wins. Tufts [Men's basketball] skins Leopards, 75-59.
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 January 27; UP029.021.032.00003 (Volume 32)
    Administration moves ahead with co-ed housing proposal. Charles Inouye names Dean of Colleges. Colonel Moshe El'ad foster discussion on mideast accord. Tufts sophmore [Anne Maurer] works full time for Bradley's campaign. Women's track crushes its competition at Gantcher. Jumbo's claim second straight quad cup.
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 January 31; UP029.021.040.00045 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 01; UP029.021.032.00004 (Volume 32)
    Thirty get whirlwind rally tour. Tufts students sought to go to symposium. Jumbos skate past Lebanon Valley College, win 4-3.
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 02; UP029.021.032.00005 (Volume 32)
    [John] McCain, [Al] Gore reign in New Hampshire. Small New Hampshire town kicks off the primary season. ELBO [Elections Board] seels to fill vacated TCU [Tufts Community Union] seats. Tufts students react to New Hampshire primary. Jumbos [women's basketball]shake off losing streak with big home victory. Jumbos [men's basketball] win fifth straight home game to remain undefeated at home.
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 03; UP029.021.032.00006 (Volume 32)
    Dibiaggio's class brings a who's-who of speakers. TTLGBC [Tufts Transgendered Lesbian Gay BI-sexual collective] alumni group endows annual scholarship at ceremony. Jumbo's [men's track] stay on track at Bowdoin. Jumbo's [women's track] nipped by Bowdoin in Quad Cup.
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 04; UP029.021.032.00007 (Volume 32)
    Many changes made at campus computing labs. Tufts students respond to wage change. Film series gets back on track. Tufts [men's swimming] bounces back from Bates loss to destroy MIT. Jumbos [Women's swimming and diving] 2-2 in eight-day stretch. Jumbo's [women's squash on upswing.
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 07; UP029.021.040.00033 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 08; UP029.021.040.00034 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 09; UP029.021.040.00035 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 10; UP029.021.040.00036 (Volume UP029 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 2000 February 11; UP029.021.032.00008 (Volume 32)
    Survey cites lack of housing as a major issue among students. TILIP [Tufts Insititute for Leadership and International Perspective] symposium brings international students together. Women swimmers end regular season on positive note. [senior Drew Carleton] has become one of the best in Tufts ice hockey history. Crucial weekend ahead for men's basketball team. Men's squash loses three straight. [freshman Emily] Goodman receives women's hoops honors.